Guide to the Jim Graham papers, 1961-2015 MS2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jim Graham/Whitman-Walker Clinic records, 1973-1998; MS2013 Series 1
  - Administrative files, 1980-1998; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Union Organizing, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - University of Maryland (Art Gallery), undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Upcoming Events, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Urban's HIV/AIDS Mayoral Platform, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Urban, Inc., 1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - USAID, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - USAID Meeting, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Video Production, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Video project: "Every Eighteen Minutes,", 1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - VIP List, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - VIP List Revision, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Issues, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Meeting, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Recognition Event, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Volunteer Recognition Event, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Recognition, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Resources, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Volunteer Services Memo, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Volunteer Training Manual- Sunnye Sherman AIDS Education Program, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Von Gloeden Report, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Washington Area Consortium for HIV in Youth (WACHIVY), undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Washington Performing Arts Society (WPAS), undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - WCXR, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Whitman- Walker Clinic Newsletter, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic of Suburban Maryland, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Wilhelm von Gloeden Exhibition, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - "With AIDS, Poland Today Is Like D.C.in '83," in The Washington Post, January 2, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - WLTT Good Lite Fund Grant Request, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Work Plans, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - YOUCCAN Project Grant Application, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Youth Services, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Youth Services, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - 3rd Party Agreement, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - 730 11th Street Draft Process, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - 1335 R Street, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - 17th Street Lease I, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - 17th Street Lease II, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - 17th Street Lease III, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - 18th Street Property, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Publications, 1978-1996; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains publications of the Whitman-Walker Clinic. The items date from 1978-96. The materials include annual reports, Whitman-Walker event programs and brochures, newsletters, and other publications related to Whitman-Walker AIDS programs.
    - AIDS Program Memorial Brochure, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alternative and Holistic Health Care for AIDS and its Prevention, October, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alternative and Holistic Health Care for AIDS and its Prevention, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report (Production Information and Drafts), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Friends for Life- Second Annual Celebration, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Friends for Life- Third Annual Spring Gala Weekend, May 3-4, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lights of the City: The Volunteers, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Newsletter, July-August, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Pastoral Ministry in the Era of AIDS: Focus on Families and Friends of Persons With AIDS, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Positive Living- A Guide to the Whitman-Walker Clinic HIV/AIDS Services", undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Newsletter, July-August, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Recognition Dinner Program, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic Honors Its Volunteers Booklet, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic's Tenth Anniversary Dinner Program, May 16, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Audio-visual materials, 1989-1998; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains audio-visual items related to the Whitman-Walker Clinic. This material dates from 1989-98. The materials include videocassettes, cassette tapes, and one compact disc. These materials document interviews, AIDS information seminars, and other Whitman-Walker AIDS-related events, such as candlelight vigils, AIDSWALKs, and AIDS Rides.
    - Video: Amadeus (?), undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Video: AIDS Marathon Training Program V-Lite videocassette, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Video: AIDS Services, July 10, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Video: "AIDS Ride Washington D.C.," BET News, Nightside (NBC), June, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Video: "AIDS Ride Washington DC," Washington Coverage, June 18-19, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Video: AIDSWALK, 6 minutes, 45 seconds, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Video: AIDSWALK, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Video: AIDSWALK, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Video: AIDSWALK, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Video: AIDSWALK Washington 1997 Team Video, 10 minutes, 30 seconds (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Video: Barney Frankly on E.N.D.A., narrated Pat Schroeder, an independent, not-for-profit P.S.A.to educate the American public about the employment Non-Discrimination Act, 2 minutes, 47 seconds, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Video: Bell Atlantic Contribution to Whitman-Walker Clinic, 2 minutes 15 seconds, December 13, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Video: Candlelight Vigil, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Video: Candlelight Vigil, ISO 2, Part 1 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Video: Candlelight Vigil, ISO 2, Part 2 of 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Video: CDJ Productions, "AIDS," "David?s Song," 5 minutes, 18 seconds, December 9, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Video: [A] Celebration of the Life of Gerald "Jerry" Brian Roemer, July 1 1965 - August 15 1997, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Video: Cf2GS - NW AIDS Foundation, Project Action - "Horn Away.", undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Video: Chrissie Hynde and Act Up: the March for Animals, 15 minutes, June 27, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Video: Circle of Support: The AIDS Network, 27 minutes, 48 seconds, November 29, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Video: Cornelia Scott (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Video: Current Issues, "AIDS Prevention," with guests Beatrice von Guggenberg and Dr.Peter Hawly, host John Milewski, C-SPAN and C-SPAN2 December 7-8, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Video: David Kamens, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Video: Development Staff Meeting, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Video: DOJ World AIDS Day, Commemoration, The Great Hall, December 6, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Video: Drugs and AIDS: Getting the Message Out, Produced by Tom Goodwin and Gerargine Wurzburg, State of the Art Productions, Washington, D.C., 27 minutes, 20 seconds, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Video: "Eating Defensively: Food Safety Advice for Persons with AIDS," 14 minutes, 30 seconds, September, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Video: Flemming-Morgan Access Center Dedication, October 5, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Video: FOX News- Press Conference, 10 o'clock news, FOX News Morning- "Be There for the Cure," with Graham and Novell, FOX Evening News, October 22 and December 1, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Video: Human Rights Campaign Fund "Your Story, Out Story," 12 minutes, March 11, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Video: JG- Channel 9, Amsterdam update, July 21, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Video: Jim Graham- WRC News at 5:00- Needle Exchange, April 24, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Video: John McLoughile (?) Appearance, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Video: Junior League of Washington, 11 minutes, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Video: Lest We Forget: the AIDS Memorial Quilt in the Capital, 30 minutes, October 11-13, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Video: Lest We Forget: the AIDS Memorial Quilt in the Capital, 30 minutes, plastic wrapped, October 11-13, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Video: Magic Johnson Follow-up Story, November 11; WUSA, September, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Video: Magic Johnson Original Shows Plus, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Video: [A] Message from Jean Dubofsky, July, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Video: "Needle Exchange: Jim Graham, Whitman-Walker Clinic," 19 seconds, April 22, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Video: News Channel 8- Interview, June 10, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Video: Philadelphia-DC AIDS Ride Comp Tape, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Video: Philadelphia-DC AIDS Ride, presented by Tanqueray, Share the Video, Boston-New York AIDS Ride 1995, 12 minutes, 40 seconds (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Video: Positive Immunity Pilot Program, The Monroe Inst.and Jim Graham, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Video: Preparing for Managed Care: Strategies for Community-Based Organizations Serving People with HIV/AIDS, Tape 1, Managed Care Basics, 105 minutes, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Video: Preparing for Managed Care: Strategies for Community-Based Organizations Serving People with HIV/AIDS, Tape 2, Developing Partnership with Managed Care Organizations and Strategic Options, 90 minutes, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Video: Preparing for Managed Care: Strategies for Community-Based Organizations Serving People with HIV/AIDS, Tape 3, The AIDS Healthcare Foundation Experience with Managed Cars and the Changing Medical System, 100 minutes, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Video: September 27, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Video: "Significant Losses.", undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Video: "Someone is Picking All the Flowers," Stained Glass Memorial Rededication, December 1, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Video: The Choice Program- NBC Nightly News, June 23, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Video: "This is America with Dennis Wholey," Dennis Wholey: America #256, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Video: Thomas Films, Whitman-Walker Clinic TV Prevention Campaign, 2 minutes, October 5, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Video: Video Seminars for AIDS Service Providers, Module I: Program Planning, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Video: Video Seminars for AIDS Service Providers, Module II: Communications, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Video: Video Seminars for AIDS Service Providers, Module III: Development and Finance, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Video: Video Seminars for AIDS Service Providers, Module IV: Management, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Video: Whitman-Walker Clinic Video, March 26, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Video: Whitman-Walker Clinic AIDS March, ISO # 1, October 10, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Video: Whitman-Walker Clinic AIDS March, ISO # 2, October 10, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Video: Whitman-Walker Clinic AIDS March, ISO # 3, October 10, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Video: 1996 National AIDS Candlelight March, Congressional Breakfast Briefing, C-SPAN2 Coverage, March 27, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Compact Disc: Hand Carved Coffins, A Mystery by Jimm Altman, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cassette Tape: AIDS: Bridget Kendall Packages, undated (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cassette Tape: Interview- WAMU, Jim Graham and K.McGee, Whitman-Walker Pharmacy, July 25, 1994 (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Cassette Tape: Jim Graham, Whitman-Walker Clinic interview with Meyer Foundation, July 12, 1994 (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Cassette Tape: MGT, February 15, 1996 (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Cassette Tape: TEC Speaker Series, Growing Customer Relationships, undated (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Cassette Tape: Washington D.C.AIDS Ride 3, 30 minutes, undated (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Cassette Tape: IX International Conference on AIDS in affiliation with the IV STD World Conference, Berlin, June 7-11, 1993 (Box SHARED Box 20, Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Videos: Unlabeled Videocassettes (2) from Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 1A, Folder 1)
  - Oversized, 1983-1996; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains items that are too large to be housed with the rest of the collection. The items in this series include photographs of Walt Whitman and Dr. Mary Walker, oversized certificates and awards granted to the Clinic, a green folder with Chinese lettering, oversized photographs and negatives, posters, and a large posterboard Acheck@ awarded to the Clinic by former Mayor Barry. The items date from 1983-1996, although the series includes two photographs that undoubtably date earlier than 1983.
    - Award- "The Government of the District of Columbia [presents] James A.Graham, a member of the D.C. Citizens Advisory Committee on Resources and Budget, this 10th day of June in the year 1983" (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Blueprint, 14th Street Elevation, design for Whitman-Walker Clinic Medical Center on the corner of 14th and R Streets, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Blueprint, R Street Elevation, design for Whitman-Walker Clinic Medical Center on the corner of 14th and R Streets, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Certificate of Recognition, awarded to the Whitman-Walker Clinic for participation in the U.S. Army Materiel Command's Combined Federal Campaign Promotion, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Chinese Folder- Light green paper, folded, with Chinese lettering on the front; picture of an old man and a piece of paper with Chinese lettering inside the folded paper, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Contact Prints- Oversized, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Negatives- Oversized, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Photograph- Jim Graham and Tipper Gore in front of Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Poster- Africa's First Full-Length Drama on AIDS, It's Not Easy, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Poster- "Preparing for Managed Care: Strategies for Community-Based Organization Serving People with HIV/AIDS.", undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Poster- "We Are Not A Colony!", undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Buttons- "AIDS Walk Washington Sat. Sept. 23 1995;" "Information to Action, METRO Teen AIDS;" "Lift the Ban;" "Miracle Worker.", undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Large Check on Posterboard- "Government of the District of Columbia, Office of Business and Economic Development, Marion Barry Jr., Mayor Pay to the Order of Whitman Walker Clinic, Inc., Five Hundred Fifty Thousand", undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Framed Blueprint, Plans for Whitman-Walker Clinic, Inc., Medical Center- R Street Elevation., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Framed Blueprint, Plans for Whitman-Walker Clinic, Inc., Medical Center- 14th Street Elevation., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Photograph- Dr. Mary Walker, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Photograph- Walt Whitman, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Exhibit materials, undated; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 3)
      General
      These appear to be for an exhibit in Special Collections using reproductions of the collection materials.
    - Poster: loveaidspeople, 1989 (Box 4A, Folder 1)
    - Poster: "The Answer Is YES!" - Asian and Pacific Islander Partnership for Health, undated (Box 4A, Folder 3)
    - Poster: "Some of us are dying to be ourselves" - Sexual Minority Youth Assistance League, undated (Box 4A, Folder 4)
    - Posters: National Candlelight - AIDS March (21 copies), 1996 October 12 (Box 4A, Folder 5)
    - Poster: "Primary Care Needs of Lesbian and Gay Adolescents", 1994 December (Box 4A, Folder 6)
    - Poster: "Self-Organisation of Male Sexworkers" (multilingual), 1992 (Box 4A, Folder 8)
    - Poster: "The Names Project AIDS Memorial Quilt: Not All Battles Are Fought With A Sword.", 1996 October (Box 4A, Folder 9)
    - Poster: "World AIDS Day 1996 Commemoration", 1996 December 6 (Box 4A, Folder 10)
    - Poster: "If He Doesn't Care Enough To Wear A Condom, He Doesn't Care.", undated (Box 4A, Folder 11)
    - Poster: "Are You Man Enough To Protect Your Lover?", undated (Box 4A, Folder 12)
    - Poster: "Only One Thing Should Come Between You And Your Lover", undated (Box 4A, Folder 13)
    - Poster: "Do the Safe Thing" - Whitman-Walker Clinic, Inc., undated (Box 4A, Folder 14)
    - Poster: Safe Sex/Condom - Male (Thai), undated (Box 4A, Folder 16)
    - Poster: Safe Sex/Condom - Female (Thai), undated (Box 4A, Folder 17)
    - AIDS Foundation of the Whitman-Walker Clinic Recognition Resolution of 1988, 1988 December 13 (Box 5A, Folder 1)
      General note
      Printed on cardboard. No cover.
    - AIDS Foundation of the Whitman-Walker Clinic Recognition Resolution of 1988, 1988 December 13 (Box 5A, Folder 2)
    - Robert N. Schwartz, M.D. Housing Services 5th Anniversary Recognition Resolution of 1990 (Box 5A, Folder 3)
    - Whitman-Walker Clinic Volunteer Contributors Recognition Resolution of 1990, 1990 May 15 (Box 5A, Folder 4)
    - Commemoration of the Lives of District of Columbia Residents Who Died of AIDS During the First Decade of the Epidemic Day Declaration Resolution of 1991, 1991 June 4 (Box 5A, Folder 5)
    - Elizabeth Taylor Medical Clinic/Whitman-Walker 20th Anniversary Recognition Resolution of 1993 (Box 5A, Folder 6)
      Also includes paper printout copy of ceremonial resolution.
    - Jim Graham Day Declaration Resolution 1994, 1994 April 12 (Box 5A, Folder 7)
      Also includes paper printout copy of ceremonial resolution 10-596.
    - Jim Graham Day Declaration Resolution 1994, 1994 April 12 (Box 5A, Folder 8)
    - Jim Graham Day Declaration Resolution 1994, 1994 April 12 (Box 5A, Folder 9)
    - Jim Graham Day Declaration Resolution 1994, 1994 April 12 (Box 5A, Folder 10)
    - Jim Graham Ten Years of Outstanding Service Recognition Resolution 1994 (Box 5A, Folder 11)
    - President Clinton's 1996 World AIDS Day Proclamation (Box 5A, Folder 12)
      Proclamation is a copy with Presidential Seal. Also includes letter form Patricia S. Fleming, Director of the Office of National AIDS Policy.
    - Photo: 3rd Annual Gay Bartenders Ball, undated (Box 5A, Folder 13)
    - Photo: Gathering in Great Room, undated (Box 5A, Folder 14)
    - Photo Book: AIDS WALK 1994 (signed) (Box 5A, Folder 15)
      Photo book is autographed by photographer. Contains 8 photographs.
    - Framed Photo: Brother to Brother Sister to Sister United & Tanqueray's American AIDSRideUSA (signed), undated (Box 5A, Folder 19)
  - Affiliated organizations, 1986-1997; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 7
    This subseries contains items related to other AIDS organizations, health care organizations, and gay and lesbian organizations, and any publications of those organizations. The items date from 1986-97. The topics include, AIDS Action annual reports; information from the Center for Disease Control; publications from global reaching AIDS-education and research organizations; District of Columbia health care plans; conference proceedings; publications from numerous HIV/AIDS related organizations, education programs, health care plans, and events.
    - AED- Academy for Education Development I, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AED- Academy for Education Development II, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AETNA Taking Part Booklet, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Agency for HIV/AIDS, Comprehensive HIV/AIDS Plan, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Annual Report, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Action Annual Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - AIDS Action 1994 Board Retreat Travel Information (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Action Update, Vol.9, No.3, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Action Council- Annual Board Retreat, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Action Council- Board Member Files, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Action Council Communication Committee, March 15, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Action Council (General), undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Action Council Legislative and Policy Goals, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Antibody Testing Pamphlet, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - AIDS Awareness Publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - AIDS Awareness Publications- Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - AIDSCAP: Behavior Change Communication for the Prevention and Treatment of STDs, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - AIDSCAP: Partnership with the Media, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - AIDSCAP: Policy and Advocacy in HIV/AIDS Prevention, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - AIDSCAP Response, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - AIDSCAP Response, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - AIDSCOM: A World Against AIDS: Communication for Behavior Change, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - AIDSCOM: Partners Against AIDS, Lessons Learned, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Control and Prevention Project, Final Report, Volume 1, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Control and Prevention Project, Final Report, Volume 2, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Health Care Delivery- Report of the Intra-governmental Task Force, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Health Promotion Risk Reduction Program For Groups at High Risk for AIDS, August 11, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Health Promotion Risk Reduction Program For Groups at High Risk for AIDS- Monthly Report, September 10, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - AIDS in San Francisco, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - AIDS in Virginia- A Public Health Report, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Legal Guide, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Program- Department of Veteran Affairs, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Project Los Angeles (APLA) Client Handbook, Winter, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - APLA "Commitment to Life VII", undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Reference Guide for Medical Professionals, Second Edition, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Sticker, "loveaidspeople", undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Summit- D.C. Comprehensive AIDS Resource and Education Consortium, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Update: A Report to the Board, c. 1995 Alcohol and Drug Abuse Service Administration (ADASA), undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation (ACLU), undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - American Council of Life Insurance- Annual Report, American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - AMFAR Annual Report, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - AMFAR Papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Americans Living With AIDS- Report, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Americans Who Care- Volunteers Working In the Battle Against AIDS, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Austin Center Photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Awareness Comic Book, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - [The] Best of Washington Social Club Inc. Program, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Primary Health Care, "Contract Checklist for Managed Care", undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Primary Health Care, "Managed Care, Internal Opportunities" Booklet, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of Primary Health Care, "Managed Care Market Area", undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Primary Health Care, "Opening the Door to Managed Care" Booklet, October, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Business and Labor Speak out on AIDS Pamphlet, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Center for Disease Control- National Conference on the Prevention of HIV Infection and AIDS, August 15-17, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)